Guide to the Nancy Ottmann Albert Papers, 1981 - 2006
Nancy Ottmann Albert Papers1981 - 2006
- Series II. Negatives
  - Binder 2: Negative book 2, 1990-1996
    - 9306 July, 1993; MA: Uxbridge, CT: Middletown; rural vernacular, houses, Barn, Wadsworth mansion (Binder 1)
    - 9307 July, 1993; CT: North Plains; rural vernacular; *Nancy Smith's barn and gas pump (Binder 1)
    - 9308 August, 1993; CT: Hartford; urban landscapes; Lewis St. (Binder 1)
    - 9309 September, 1993; CT: Haddam; rural, roadside vernacular; *Shad Shack, gas pump (Binder 1)
    - 9310 September, 1993; CT: Hartford; urban landscapes; Bartholomew St., factories (Binder 1)
    - 9311 September, 1993; CT: Middletown; houses; Wadsworth Mansion before restoration (Binder 1)
    - 9312 September, 1993; MA: Ware, Worcester; urban landscapes, mills (Binder 1)
    - 9313 September, 993; MA: Worcester; R.R. Stations, urban vernacular; pre-restoration (Binder 1)
    - 9314 September, 1993; MA: Worcester; R.R. Station, mills (Binder 1)
    - 9315 October, 1993; CT: Hartford; bridges, Polish Home; *Charter Oak Bridge demolition (Binder 1)
    - 9401 Nov., 1993-January, 1994; CT: New Britain, Portland, Haddam; rural, roadside vernacular; *Portland Drive-In (Binder 1)
    - 9402 January, 1994; CT: Middletown; mental hospitals; *CVH winter scenes (Binder 1)
    - 9403 January, 1994; CT: Hartford, Middletown; mills, mental hospitals; Royal Factory demolition, CVH (Binder 1)
    - 9404 January, 1994; CT: Middletown; CFA; winter scenes (Binder 1)
    - 9405 January, 1994; CT: Middletown; CFA; winter scenes (Binder 1)
    - 9406 April, 1994; CT: Middletown, Durham; urban vernacular, houses; Middletown, diner, *Durham house (Binder 1)
    - 9407 April, 1994; CT: Middletown; CFA; spring scenes (Binder 1)
    - 9408 April, 1994; CT: Middletown; CFA; spring photos (Binder 1)
    - 9409 July, 1994; CT: Watertown, S. Glastonbury; houses, rural vernacular; Harkness, Maiden Lane (Binder 1)
    - 9410 October, 1994; CT: Middletown, Berlin; houses, landscape, quarry; R. House, Worthington Mtg. House (Binder 1)
    - Lake Ohrachobee area Florida, 1994 (Binder 1)
      1 sheet, 34 negatives
    - Missouri Jan. 1995 (Binder 1)
      2 sheets, 63 negatives
    - 9501 Nov. 1994-February, 1995; CT: Portland, Lyme area; rural and urban vernacular; New Dawn Dairy (Binder 1)
    - 9502 March, 1995; MA: Holyoke; urban landscapes; storefront. very thin negatives (Binder 1)
    - 9503 March-July, 1995; CT: Lyme area, ME; houses, cemetaries (Binder 1)
    - 9504 July 3, 1995; RI, CT: Baltic, Middletown; mills, churches, vernacular, includes Baltic Mill (Binder 1)
    - 9503 July 3, 1995; CT: Yantic, RI: Rockville; textile mills, vernacular (Binder 1)
    - 9506 July, 1995; CT: Baltic; textile mills; Baltic Mill before fire (Binder 1)
    - 9507 September, 1995; CT: North Grosvenordale, Rockville; textile mills; *NGD mills on low water canal (Binder 1)
      1 sheet, 7 negatives
    - 9508, 1995; VT, Windsor, White River Junction; urban and rural vernacular (Binder 1)
    - 9509 September, 1995; CT: Notfolk area; houses, mills (Binder 1)
    - 9510 October, 1995; MA: Pittsfield North Adams; urban and rural vernacular; very high contrast (Binder 1)
    - 9511 October, 1995; MA: Mohawk Trail areal; roadside vernacular, cabins; also Wadsworth Mansion (Binder 1)
    - 9512 October, 1995; NY: Saratoga area; houses, vernacular; also includes CFA (Binder 1)
    - 9513 October, 1995; VT, MA: Bernardston; roadside-vernacular; inn, motel, church (Binder 1)
    - 9514 Dec. 1995-Jan. 1996; CT: Middletown, Portland; roadside vernacular; includes old farm equipment (Binder 1)
    - 9601 September, 1996; MA: Slaterville, Uxbridge; textile mills, Stanley Woolen Mill; *good images, spools. R. House (Binder 1)
    - 9602 September, 1996; MA: Uxbridge; textile mills; *good images (Binder 1)
    - 9603 September, 1996; CT: North Grosvenordale area; milltowns, vernacular; includes worker housing (Binder 1)
    - 9604 October, 1996; MA, RI: Pawtucket area; roadside vernacular, churches (Binder 1)
    - 9605 November 16, 1996; RI: Blackstone River area; roadside vernacular, theaters; *LeRoy Theater (Binder 1)
    - 9606 November 16, 1996; RI: Blackstone River area; roadside vernacular, drive-ins, mills, good negatives (Binder 1)
    - May-July 1993 (Binder 1)
      1 envelope, 25 negative sheets
  - Binder 3: Negative book 3, Europe, 1992-2002
    - E9101 May, 1991; Amsterdam; streets, architecture; canals, doorways (Binder 1)
    - E9102 May, 1991; Amsterdam; street scenes, canals; very thin negatives (Binder 1)
    - E9103 June, 1991; France: Amiens; Churches, architecture, Cathedral, half-timbered houses (Binder 1)
    - E9104 June, 1991; France: Rouen; churches, architecture, cathedral, streets (Binder 1)
    - E9105 June, 1991; France: Caen, Normandy; churches, roadside vernacular, Mont St. Michel, rural scenes (Binder 1)
    - E9106 June, 1991; France: Normandy, Brittany; churches, Mont St. Michel (Binder 1)
    - E9107 June, 1991; France: Brittany; roadside and rural vernacular; *ruined barn (Binder 1)
    - E9108 June, 1991; France: Carnac, Chartres; architecture, churches, megalithic monuments, cathedral (Binder 1)
    - E9109 June, 1991; France: Chartres, Paris; chruches, city scenes, Cathredal, Paris windows, mime (Binder 1)
    - E9110 June, 1991; France, paris; churches, canals, Canal St. Martin (Binder 1)
    - E9111 June, 1991; France, Paris; urban architecture, churches, Notre Dame (Binder 1)
    - E9112 June, 1991; France: Paris; street scenes, people, churches; *Man in doorway, women/fountain (Binder 1)
    - E9201 July, 1992; France, Les Gras; churches, cemeteries, village scenes, *cemetery (Binder 1)
    - E9202 July, 1992; France: Les Gras, Paris; urban and rural architecture, Aqueduct **Atget Passageway (Binder 1)
    - E9203 July, 1992; France: Paris; architecture, churches, Pont Neuf, St. Michel statue (Binder 1)
    - E9204 July, 1992; France: Les Gras; rural vernacular, village scenes (Binder 1)
    - France, July 1992 (Binder 1)
      1 sheet, 42 negatives
    - France July 1992 (Binder 1)
    - France 1992 (Binder 1)
      1 sheet, 30 negatives
    - France 1992 (Binder 1)
      1 sheet, 20 negatives
    - E9401 May, 1994; France: Paris; urban architecture, churches, Rue St. Jacques area (Binder 1)
    - E9402 May, 1994; France, Paris; architecture, churches, Notre Dame, left bank (Binder 1)
    - E9403 May, 1994; France, Paris, architecture, parks, Jardin de Plantes (Binder 1)
    - E9404 May, 1994; France: Paris; streets; *Jardin de Plantes, Gobelin area (Binder 1)
    - E9405 May, 1994; France: Paris; architecture, streets, Chatlet, Rue St. Denis (Binder 1)
    - E9406 May, 1994; France, Paris; architecture, streets, Marais and east (Binder 1)
    - E9407 May, 1994; France: Paris; streets, parks; *Luxumbourg Gardens, Cluny (Binder 1)
    - E9408 May, 1994; France: paris; architecture, statues, D'Orsay, Marais area (Binder 1)
    - E9409 May, 1994; France: Paris; architecture, Marais, Halles aux Ble (Binder 1)
    - E9410 May, 1994; France: Paris; streets, parks, Palais Royale, *Gallerie Vivienne (Binder 1)
    - E9411 May, 1994; France: Paris; architecture, Right Bank, Bourse, Opera (Binder 1)
    - E9412 May, 1994; France: Paris, Bourges; streets, churches, rural vernacular, Au Printemps, Bourges cathedral (Binder 1)
    - E9413 May, 1993; France: South central area; churches, Abbaye Noir Lac (Binder 1)
    - E9414 May, 1994; France: central mountains, rural architecture, small mountain villages (Binder 1)
    - E9415 May, 1994; France: Cordes; rural architecture, streets, passages, doorways (Binder 1)
    - E9416 May, 1994; France: Cordes, St. Gilles; churches, streets, ruins, *bestial statues, church in St. Gilles (Binder 1)
    - E9417 May, 1994; France: St. Gilles, Arles; architecture, Pont Au Gard (Binder 1)
    - E9418 May, 1994; France, Arles, Spain; Architecture, churches, Maison Caree, Barcelona streets (Binder 1)
    - E9419 May, 1994; Spain: Barcelona; architecture, street scenes, Bari Gothic (Binder 1)
    - Paris May, 1994 (Binder 1)
      1 sheet, 32 negatives
    - Paris May, 1994 (Binder 1)
      1 sheet, 17 negatives
    - Paris May, 1994 (Binder 1)
      1 sheet, 28 negatives
    - Paris--May, 1994 (Binder 1)
    - Avignon, Bourges, France May, 1994 (Binder 1)
      1 sheet, 36 negatives
    - France St. Gilles, Avignon, Arles May, 1994 (Binder 1)
      1 sheet, 39 negatives
    - E9601 March, 1996; France: Paris; Streets, churches, Luxombourg Gardens, *man in rain (Binder 1)
    - E9602 March, 1996; France, Paris; architecture, streets, arcades, Left Bank, Coeur de Rohan (Binder 1)
    - E9603 March, 1996; France, Paris; architecture, streets, bridges, Il St. Louis (Binder 1)
    - E9604 March, 1996; France, Nantes area; churches, architecture, arcadsey; Abbaye at Nantes (Binder 1)
    - E9605 March, 1996; France, Sainte; Churches, streets, passageways, Chez Pierre (Binder 1)
    - E9606 March, 1996; France; architecture, ruins, Roman ampitheater (Binder 1)
    - E9607 March, 1996; France: Sainte; churches, rural vernacular; *Abbaye-aux-Dames, quarry (Binder 1)
      1 sheet, 1 negatives
    - E9608 March, 1996; France: Cognac, Perigeaux; architecture, churches (Binder 1)
    - E9609 March, 1996; France: Perigaux, Sarlat; churches, streets, *cathedral, one missing strip (Binder 1)
    - E9610 March, 1996; France: Sarlat; Architecture, streets, *Sunday morning in Sarlat (Binder 1)
    - E9611 March, 1996; France: Sarlat, Lascaux; architecture (Binder 1)
    - E9612 March, 1996; France: Languedoc; churches, L'Abbaye Fonteuraud (Binder 1)
    - E9613 March, 1996; France: Chartres; churches, architecture, cathedral (Binder 1)
    - France March, 1996 (Binder 1)
      2 sheets, 36 negatives
    - E9701 March, 1997; Portugal: Lisbon; architecture, streets, doorways and narrow streets (Binder 1)
    - E9702 March, 1997; Portugal: Lisbon, Obidos; churches, street scenes, Obidos vista (Binder 1)
    - E9703 March, 1997; Portugal: Buscao, Marvao; streets, architecture, Busaco Castle, morning in Marvao (Binder 1)
    - E9704 March, 1997; Portugal: Marvao; rural vernacular, streets, village streets and passageways (Binder 1)
    - E9705 march, 1997; Portugal: Marvao, Evora; streets, architecture, *stairs with closelines, Roman ruins (Binder 1)
    - E9706 March, 1997; Portugal: Evora; streets, ruins, *courtyard (Binder 1)
    - E9707 March, 1997; Portugal: Evora; architecture, churches, castle (Binder 1)
    - E9708 March, 1997; Portugal: Evora, Palmela; architecture, churches, *ruined churchyard (Binder 1)
    - E9801 March, 1998; Spain: Bourgos; churches, streets, *cathedral (Binder 1)
    - E9802 March, 1998; Spain: Sta. Domingo d.l. Calzada; churches, architecture, Guggenheim Museum at Bilbao (Binder 1)
    - E9803 March, 1998; Spain: Bilbao; architecture, Guggenheim Museum (Binder 1)
    - E9804 March, 1998; Spain: Santilliana del Mark; churches, architecture, *romanesque church (Binder 1)
    - E9805 March, 1998; Spain: Santiliana del Mar; churches, statuary, exterior/interior views of church (Binder 1)
    - E9806 March, 1998; Spain: Santilliana del Mar, Comidas; churches, architecture, romanesque churches, stork nests (Binder 1)
    - E9807 March, 1998; Spain: Comidas, Segovia; architecture, churches, cathedral, el Alcazar (Binder 1)
    - E9809 March, 1998; Spain: Segovia; architecture, churches, romanesque church, aqueduct (Binder 1)
    - E9808 March, 1998; Spain: Segovia; churches, courtyards, *cloister interior (Binder 1)
    - E9810 March, 1998; Spain: Avila; architecture, churches, *doorways, courtyard (Binder 1)
    - E0001 March, 2000; Italy: Tuscany, Greve; architecture, South of Florence (Binder 1)
    - E0002 March, 2000; Italy: Siena area; architecture, cityscape; along Rte. 222, the "Chiantina" (Binder 1)
    - E0003 March, 2000; Italy: Buenconvento, Pienza; street scenes, *passageways (Binder 1)
    - E0004 March, 2000; Italy: Montepulchiano, San Gimmiano; architecture, streets, churches (Binder 1)
    - E0005 March, 2000; Italy: San Gimmiano; architecture, streets, towers (Binder 1)
    - E0006 March, 2000; Italy: Piltigano; architecture, city views, piazzas (Binder 1)
    - E0007 March, 2000; Italy: Piitlgano; street scenes, vistas, *passageways (Binder 1)
    - E0008 March, 2000; Italy: San Galgano; churches, *roofless Abbey at San Galgano (Binder 1)
    - E0009 March, 2000; Italy: Siena, architecture, churches, passageways and courtyards (Binder 1)
    - E0010 March, 2000; Italy: Siena, Florence; architecture, churches, *piazza in rain (Binder 1)
    - E0011 March, 2000; Italy: Florence; churches, architecture, cathedral (Binder 1)
    - E0012 March, 2000; Italy: Flroence, St. Rocco a Pilli; bridges, architecture, barns, Ponte Vecchio, villa barn (Binder 1)
    - E0013 March, 2000; Italy: Volterra; street scenes, churches, *bestial statues in cathedral (Binder 1)
    - E0014 March, 2000; Italy: Volterra; architecture, streets, people, *women walking (Binder 1)
    - E0015 March, 2000; italy: Venice; architecture, people, *Piazza San Marco (Binder 1)
    - E0016 March, 2000; italy: venice; architecture, churches (Binder 1)
    - E0017 March, 2000; Italy: Venice; architecture, churches, along the Grand Canale (Binder 1)
    - E0018 March, 2000; Italy: Venice, Murano; architecture, *boat in canal, market (Binder 1)
    - E0019 March, 2000; Italy; Venice, Murano; churches, piazzas (Binder 1)
    - E0020 March, 2000; italy: Venice; architecture, street and water scenes, Rialto Market, *passageways (Binder 1)
    - E0021 March, 2000; Italy: Venice; architecture, people, fish and vegtable market (Binder 1)
    - E0023 March, 2000; Italy: Venice; architectural, street scenes, San Paolo (Binder 1)
    - E0024 March, 2000; Italy: Venice; arhitecture, canals, *good image with boat (Binder 1)
    - E0025 March, 2000; Italy, Venice; architecture, churches, cloister (Binder 1)
    - E0201 July, 2002; Prague; architecture, churches, St. Vitus cathedral (Binder 1)
    - E0202 July, 2002; Prague; architecture, cemeteries, *Joslof area, Jewish Cemetery (Binder 1)
    - E0203 July, 2002; Prague; architecture, bridges, Old Town, *Charles Bridge (Binder 1)
    - E0204 July, 2002; Prague; architecture, Mila Strana area (Binder 1)
    - E0205 July, 2003; Prague; architecture, art nouveau, cubist and Gehry buildings (Binder 1)
    - E0206 July, 2002; Pilsen, Germany: Nurenberg; architecture, churches (Binder 1)
    - E0207 July, 2002; Germany: Main and Danube Canals; waterworks, scenes from on board ship (Binder 1)
    - E0208 July, 2002; Germany: Regensburg; architecture, passageways and courtyards (Binder 1)
    - E0209 July, 2002; Germany: Passau; architecture, *passageways, street scenes (Binder 1)
    - E0210 July, 2002; Germany: Passau; street scenes, *passageways and narrow streets (Binder 1)
    - E0211 July, 2002; Germany: Passau; architecture, rivers, *narrow street with bicycle (Binder 1)
    - E0212 July, 2002; Germany: Melk; rivers, churches, Abbey at Melk, Danube River (Binder 1)
    - E0213 July, 2002; Austria: Wauchau Valley and Vienna; architecture, churches, *Haas Haus, St. Stephens (Binder 1)
    - E0214 July, 2002; Vienna; architecture, *Palm Haus and Karlsplatz station (Binder 1)
    - E0215 July, 2002; Viena, Budapest; architecture, bridges, Gallerie, Vienna (Binder 1)
    - E0216 July, 2002; Budapest; architecture, people, *covered market (Binder 1)
    - E0217 July, 2003; Budapest; architecture, bridges, pest castle (Binder 1)
    - Paris/France, July 1992 (Binder 1)
      1 envelope, 11 negative sleeves
  - Binder 4: Negative book 4, 1998-1999
    - 9801 March, 1998; CT: Middletown; houses, Russell House, test roll with new Fuji camera (Binder 1)
    - 9802 June 8 and 9, 1998; MA: Boston, RI: Lonsdale; urban landscape, milltowns, his was the new beginning (Binder 1)
    - 9803 June 9, 1998; RI: Lonsdale; milltowns, roadside vernacular, *includes drive-in (Binder 1)
    - 9305 June 9, 1998; RI: West Warwick; textile mills, milltowns, *Royal Mill (Binder 1)
    - 9805 June 9, 1998; RI: West Warwick area, textile mills, *Royal and Lippitt Mills (Binder 1)
    - 9806 June 9, 1998; RI: West Warwick, CT: Voluntown; textile mills, roadside vernacular, *Harris, Hope, *Griswold airport (Binder 1)
    - 9807 June 1998; CT: Hartford, RI: Watch Hill; urban landscapes, hotels (Binder 1)
    - 9408 June 1998; RI: Watch Hill; hotels, roadside vernacular, *inn, *gas pumps (Binder 1)
    - 9809 Jule 1998; NH: Hanover area; rural vernacular, houses (Binder 1)
    - 9810 July 1998; NH: Hanover area; houses, bridges, *very good images (Binder 1)
    - 9811 July 1998; NH: Lisbon, Cheever, Hillsborough; rural vernacular, churhces, *Cheever church, Hillsborough houses (Binder 1)
    - 9412 July 1998; NH: Harrisville; textile mills, houses, *excellent images (Binder 1)
    - 9813 July 1998; NH: Harrisville; textile mills, mill towns, *excellent images (Binder 1)
    - 9814 July, 26, 1998; RI: along Rte. 1; roadside vernacular, drive-ins, Hill-Top Drive-In, Quonset Point (Binder 1)
    - 9815 July 26, 1998; RI: E. Greenwich, eastern towns; textile mills, milltowns, Hamilton and Lafayette Mills (Binder 1)
    - 9816 July 26, 1998; RI: Shannock; textile mills, *excellent water images (Binder 1)
    - 9817 July 26, 1998; RI: Shannock, Westerly; textile mills, *mystery wooden mill, White Rock (Binder 1)
    - 9818 August 23, 1998; MA: North Adams; milltowns, includes MassMoca site (Binder 1)
    - 9819 August 23, 1998; MA: North Adams; milltowns (Binder 1)
    - 9819 August 28, 1998; RI: Valley Falls, Ashton; milltowns, textile mills, Kennedy, Valley Falls, Central mills (Binder 1)
    - 9821 August 27, 1998; RI: Woonsockett, Georgiaville; milltowns (Binder 1)
    - 9822 August 28, 1998; RI: Woonsockett area; milltowns (Binder 1)
    - 9823 August 28, 1998; RI: Warwock area; textile mills, Anthony, Pontiac Mills (Binder 1)
    - 9824 August 29, 1998; RI: Providence area; milltowns, Olneyville Mill. very high contrast (Binder 1)
    - 9825 September 27, 1998; CT: Granby, MA: Easthampton; vernacular, milltowns (Binder 1)
    - 9826 September 27, 1998; MA: Easthampton, Northampton; mental hospitals, *the start of the hospital project (Binder 1)
    - 9827 September 27, 1998; MA: Northampton: mental hospitals, *excellent images (Binder 1)
    - 9828 September 27, 1998; MA: Northampton; mental hospitals, *excellent images (Binder 1)
    - 9829 Sept.-Oct. 1998; MA: Easthapmton, CT: Norwich; milltowns, mental hospitals; *Majestic Theater, Norwich State (Binder 1)
    - 9830 October 11, 1998; CT: Norwich; mental hospitals, *includes barber chair (Binder 1)
    - 9831 October 11, 1998; CT: Norwich; mental hospitals, *great images (Binder 1)
    - 9832 October 11, 1998; CT: Taftville; textile mills, Ponomeh Mill (Binder 1)
    - 9833 October 11, 1998; CT: Baltic; textile mills, milltowns, *very good images (Binder 1)
    - 9834 October 17, 1998; NC: Charlotte area; vernacular houses, *houses with rocking chairs (Binder 1)
    - 9835 October 1998; SC: York, CT: Hartford; houses, urban vernacular, Ann Street area (Binder 1)
    - 9836 October 28, 1998; CT: Hartford, Ann Street; urban vernacular, *International Barber Shop (Binder 1)
    - 9837 November 8, 1998; CT: Hartford; houses, urban vernacular, Trinity area, Goodwin mansion (Binder 1)
    - 9838 November 15, 1998; CT: Hartford, Middletown; bridges, urban vernacular, *CT River from Arrigoni Bridge (Binder 1)
    - 9839 November 1998; CT: Middletown, Hartford; urban vernacular, Park Street area (Binder 1)
    - 9840 November 18, 1998; CT: Hartford; urban vernacular, street scenes, Park and Broad St. area (Binder 1)
    - 9841 November 18, 1998; CT: Hartford; street scenes, urban vernacular, *includes two girls (Binder 1)
    - 9842 November 1998; CT: Hartford, Middletown; urban vernacular, nridges, Park St., R.R. Bridge, Middletown (Binder 1)
    - 9843 november 27, 1998; CT: Middletown; mental hospitals, Connecticut Valley Hospital (Binder 1)
    - Guide to Negatives--1999 (Binder 1)
      1 sheet
    - 9901 January 16, 1999; CT: Berlin, Hartford; roadside vernacular, churches, Worthington Meeting House (Binder 1)
    - 9902 Feb.-March 1999; CT: Hartford, London; urban architecture, Drive-In, Greenwich Observatory (Binder 1)
    - 9903 March 1999; London, Greenwich; urban architecture; Royal Observatory, Kew Gardens (Binder 1)
    - 9304 March-April, 1999; London, MA: Southwich; urban architecture, rural vernacular, Kew Gardens, migrant labor camp (Binder 1)
    - 9305 April 1999; MA: Southwick; rural vernacular, *migrant labor camp--good images (Binder 1)
    - 9906 April, 1999; CT: Thomaston; Mills, RR station, *good shots of RR station (Binder 1)
    - 9907 April, 1999; CT: Thomaston, Rte. 8; Roadside vernacular, RR Station, highway bridge (Binder 1)
    - 9908 May 16, 1999; CT: Newtown, South Britain; mental hospitals, vernacular, *Fairfield Hills Hospital (Binder 1)
    - 9909 May 16, 1999; CT: Newtown; mental hospitals, *Fairfield Hills, ivy on porch (Binder 1)
    - 9910 May 16, 1999; CT: Newtown, Housatonic River; mental hospitals, waterworks, also abandoned houses (Binder 1)
    - 9911 may-June, 1999; CT: Naugatuck, MA: Southwick; urban and rural vernacular, migrant worker camp (Binder 1)
    - 9912 June, 1999; MA: Southwick, Indian Orchard; rural vernacular, mills, *apple orchard near Belchertown (Binder 1)
    - 9913 June, 1999; MA: Belchertown; mental hospitals, *Belchertown State School (Binder 1)
    - 9914 June, 1999; MA: Belchertown; mental hospitals; *State School for Mentally Retarded (Binder 1)
    - 9915 June 6, 1999; MA: Thorndike, Ware; mills, waterworks, also start of Long River Village (Binder 1)
    - 9916 June, 1999; CT: Middletown, NY; houses projects, roadside, start of LRV project (Binder 1)
    - 9917 June, 1999; VT, CT: Middletown; housing projects, *the start of something great (Binder 1)
    - 9918 June, 1999; CT: Middletown, Collinsville; housing projects, waterworks, Collinsville Axe factory (Binder 1)
    - 9919 June, 1999; CT: Collinsville, Torington; mills, roadside vernacular, along old Rte. 8 (Binder 1)
    - 9920 June, 1999; CT: Torrington, Middletown; housing projects, vernacular, *overturned lawn chairs (Binder 1)
    - 9921 Jule, 1999; CT: Middletown; housing projects, Long River Village (Binder 1)
    - 9922 July, 1999; CT: Middletown; housing projects, mental hospitals, LRV and CVH (Binder 1)
    - 9923 July 28, 1999; CT: Middletown; housing projects, Long River Village (Binder 1)
    - 9924 July-Aug. 1999; CT: Middletown; housing projecs, demolition begins (Binder 1)
    - 9925 August 6, 1999; CT: Middletown; housing projects, LRV (Binder 1)
    - 9926 August 6-11, 1999; CT: Middletown; housing projects, LRV: the arrival of the cat (Binder 1)
    - 9927 August 13, 1999; CT: Middletown; housing projects, Long River Village (Binder 1)
    - 9928 August 15, 1999; CT: Middletown, Willimantic; housing projects, mills, LRV, Willimantic Thread Mill (Binder 1)
    - 9929 August 15, 1999; CT: Willimantic area; mills, roadside vernacular, along Rte. 207 (Binder 1)
    - 9930 August 15; CT: Willimantic, Baltic; roadside vernacular; *two "behemouths' (Binder 1)
    - 9931 August 15, 1999; CT: Baltic, Groton; mills, roadside vernacular, Baltic Mill after fire (Binder 1)
    - 9932 August, 1999; CT: Groton, Middletown; bridges, housing projects, under Rte. 95 (Binder 1)
    - 9933 August 1999; CT: Middletown, MA: N. Adams; milltowns, housing projects, LRV near MassMoca (Binder 1)
    - 9934 August 22, 1999; MA: North Adams; milltowns, MassMoca site (Binder 1)
    - 9935 August 22, 1999; MA: North Adams; milltowns, *MassMoca, canals (Binder 1)
    - 9936 August, 1999; CT: New Canaan, Middletown; roadside vernacular, also LRV (Binder 1)